Simone Braun

453 First Road, Chicago, IL45678 s.braun@myemail.com (234) 567-8901

Committed Library page with 10+ years of experience providing excellent customer service and operational support in academic and Legal Libraries. Works efficiently under own initiative and with colleagues and possesses a talent for supporting community outreach events. Organized and efficient with a keen personal interest in modern British literature.

Education

Associate of Science in Library Technical Assistance Dominican University, River Forest, Il September 2008 -June 2010

Key Skills

- Customer service
- Digital resource management
- Alphabetical and numerical material organization
- Strong knowledge of health and safety best practice in the workplace
- Detailed understanding of library procedures

Professional Experience

Library Page

Cook County Illinois, Chicago, IL | September 2014 - Present

- Assist with database training for visitors and new staff members and provide ongoing support
- Organize and shelve legal books and documents and actively improve the shelving system, improving user satisfaction scores by 22% in 2020
- Staff the front desk and carryout book loans and returns, chasing up Late and missing items according to library policies
- Support the librarians with public outreach projects to promote the library's special collections, contributing to an uptake increase of 65% Last year

Library Page

East Chicago Public Library, Chicago, IL | July 2010 - September 2014

- Organized returns and reshelved materials using the Dewey decimal system, regularly checking to ensure that resources were attractively presented and easy to find
- Facilitated user requests in-person and via telephone and email, including locating resources in secure storage
- Performed cleaning duties and tidied public areas at the end of each shift
- Created displays to advertise educational events and promoted initiatives in-person to users